Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 14
Is it possible...
I wonder if it's possible, Father.
Can't you give everything up?
Also, the position of Hong Joo Ga's Chairman,
Can't you step down from it?
Maybe that could be the easiest way out.
It's much easier letting go of it than trying to hold onto it.
I also have a dream, if my father only does that for me...
What you, Gyung and I did to Dae Seong True Winemakers...
I'll reveal everything and take responsibility for it all.
After I set up the company to the extent that it was when Ajusshi was alive.
With Father who is no longer of the Hongju Corporation
in a small house, I will look after you.
I will play Baduk with you and fish.
This is really one in ten thousand but if by any chance...
A certain brat forgives me,
I'll plead on my knees and beg you to take her in as your daughter-in-law,
and we'll give you pocket money from what we earn.
When my child is born, you can help us raise them.
That's how I'd love to live.
Father, can't give everything up like that?
Can't you do it for me, Father?
Please answer me. Can't you do that for me, Father?
That fact that you fainted after hearing I would leave you
probably means you don't want to lose me either.
Isn't that right, Father? Isn't it?!
I can't let go.
I won't.
I won't do anything to you.
So, from now on don't try to touch me either.
Whatever unlimited responsibility you feel towards Dae Seong True Winemakers,
whether you live your life as Dae Seong True Winemaker's protector, or as a mere fisherman,
I won't care about all that anymore.
However... Although I won't lift a finger against you, Gi Jeong will be different.
Gi Jeong will shake you.
If it comes to be too much, you'll also need me to fight back.
You can go.
Don't you have to get back to protecting Dae Seong True Winemakers?
I can't lean on you?
Go ahead.
I'm heartbroken, Mom.
Officially.
There's someone I like.
You didn't know, right?
That person rejected me.
I drove her into the neighborhood, but how could I get any closer than this?
You come and bring her home.
I'm leaving.
Ajusshi.
Do you have a place to go?
Put it away!
If you need money, don't go to Noona's mom. Contact me instead.
I'll be fine!
Don't ever come here, just tell me to meet you wherever you are.
Got it?
Noona, are you okay?
♫ In the solitude which wakes me up ♫
♫ when I wake up from an exhausted sleep ♫
♫ because I still remember you smiling ♫
♫ I'm secretly smiling ♫
♫ Love leaves again this way ♫
♫ When the beautiful season arrives ♫
♫ In the sadness you left in the longing ♫
♫ I walk this street again ♫
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear, ah ♫
♫  I can't bear it ♫
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
Unni.
Can you keep me company?
Why?
I...got rejected by the man I like.
I got rejected.
Can you keep me company?
My heart...
really feels like it's been torn apart, Unni.
Jeong Woo.
Jeong Woo!
I have something to say.
Tell him to come out.
Jeong Woo, are you asleep?
Let your roommate come out.
You said you would take care of her!
You said you would look after her.
How can you abandon her now?
How can you do that to someone who already feels like their skin has come off?
Do you know what kind of girl she is?
Although she knows Mom and I aren't on her side, and keep pushing her away,
she still thinks it's a blessing to have a sister and mother like that.
There was only one person she could openly like with all her heart.
Did you have to do that to her?
Are you done with your nonsense?
What?
Do I have to accept her? No matter the circumstances?
Am I supposed to like a kid that I've never seen as a woman
just because she likes me no matter what?
Am I supposed to disregard my own feelings?
Why? Because I'm indebted to Ajusshi?
I should accept her to repay my debts?
Is that how you repay your debts?
- Why does it have to be now—
- Stop.
Don't say it, you brat.
Do you really mean what you're saying?
Can you really put your hand on your heart and say it's true?
Is this really what you want to say to me?
Do you want me to say
"You're right, I was wrong. I'll accept Hyo Seon. What do you want me to do?" in front of you?
Is that really what you want to hear?
Is that what you really want?
Then what do I really feel?
- You know it.
- What?
- Yeah, what?
You... I...
You try saying such things to me again.
If you say that to me again,
my urge to be shameless and throw away everything will surface
and make me want to forget everything,
disregard Ajusshi's kindness, disregard my sins, and just throw it all aside.
All I need is you.
As long as I have you,
I can live on and shamelessly forget all my sins.
That's really all I want.
Hyo Seon....
Is that really what you want?
Huh?
Huh?!
♫ Again today my memory led me astray ♫
♫ I who am strolling at the end of the street ♫
♫ where you can't hold me again ♫
I can't, Eun Jo.
♫ I ask again about the way ♫
It's already too late.
I can't.
You may not understand, but I can't.
♫ It must be you ♫
Although it's so unfair that it drives me crazy,
♫ I cannot be without you. ♫
I can't.
♫ Like this for another day, month or year. ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
♫ My bruised heart ♫
Please reconsider Hyo Seon.
♫ I can find you.  ♫
If she suffers any more,
I really don't think I can handle it.
♫ Come to me. ♫
♫ Even if I live again ♫
♫ No matter how many times I am reborn ♫
♫ There isn't a day that I can live without you. ♫
♫ The love I will protect ♫
♫ The love I love ♫
♫ Because for me ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
♫ because you are the only one I love. ♫
Come back safely.
I will.
Did you take enough samples?
Yeah.
It'll definitely succeed if we use that machine, right?
I'll try my best.
You have to keep your promise to hang out with me when you're back.
I will.
Noona, get in. There's not much time left before the flight.
Come back safely.
There's still a lot of work to do at the winery.
I know.
You're responsible for it all while Eun Jo is in Japan.
I got it.
You go ahead first. I have to go back and get something.
Dong Soo, it's me.
How is the favor I asked you for going?
Okay.
Please keep working on it for me. I'll be waiting.
What favor?
You don't need to know.
How long are you going for?
Huh?
I asked you how long you're going for?
What did you say?
Never mind. It's okay.
You try saying those words to me again.
If you say that to me again,
my urge to be shameless and throw away everything will surface
and make me want to forget everything,
disregard Ajusshi's kindness, disregard my sins, and just throw it all to the side.
All I need is you.
As long as I have you,
I can live on and shamelessly forget all my sins.
That's all I want.
Where is she now?
Wait a moment. Don't tell her that it was me...
Joon Soo's mom, are you inside?!
What brings you here so suddenly without calling first?
Please go in.
What do you mean, Aunt?
I already heard about it before I came so don't even think about denying it.
Quietly pack your bags and leave this house.
To pack my bags?
What do you mean by that?
For the last 8 years, you've been deceiving Hyo Seon's father
and you've been leading a double life, haven't you?!
Pardon?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to say anything else.
Because you're the mother of Joon Soo,
I'll keep the secret from my Hyo Seon and everyone else,
so be grateful that I am agreeing to keep my mouth shut
and leave this house immediately.
No, Aunt. I have no idea what you're talking about.
Aigoo, my poor nephew!
Only the person gone is pitiful.
I knew one day something like this would happen,
I just knew it!
Aigoo, what a disgrace to our family!
Stop making such a ruckus! Do you have any evidence?
I asked if you have any evidence.
If you can find evidence of my double life, bring it to me!
This manipulative fox!
Who said that?
Who are you to be looking for dirt on someone as clean as myself!
I gave birth to Joon Soo.
President Goo Dae Seong's son Goo Joon Soo. I was the one who gave birth to him!
Why should I pack my bags?
I know you haven't liked me for a long time, but you doing this to me, it is too much!
- This little bitch!
- Oh my, oh my! What are you doing?
What are you going? Get up!
Come on, let go!
You little!
Why are you doing this?
I wonder if it's possible to feel more wronged.
She hasn't liked me since I stepped foot in this house.
She's trying to kick me out as soon as Joon Soo's dad passed.
She cursed me with words one shouldn't ever speak!
I feel so wronged I don't know what to do!
What?
Yes, Auntie Choi Jang!
Yes?
Yes. Please call me back then.
Hello?
Hello, Hyo Seon's Grandfather.
This is Hyo Seon's Mother. You haven't been ill in all this time, right?
It's just that I've suddenly experienced something so terrible,
I didn't know what to do but thought you,
who have always helped me out,
would know what sort of advice to give me.
I feel so wronged I don't know what to do!
I'm telling you that's what happened! Why can't you understand what I'm saying?
I'm telling you that's what I heard.
I'm sure I heard her planning something
with the older daughter and the kid here!
And what did you hear her say?
So this is something that you started, Hyo Seon's uncle.
Ah, well...
- Hyo Seon's Uncle.
- Yes?
Do you want me gone from this house?
- No, you see...
- Do you know who I am?
- What?
- Do you have any idea how Hyo Seon's father thought of me?
I'm not sure what you misheard and why you're doing this to me,
Even if it's the truth,
you're in no position to say this to me.
This shouldn't be coming from you.
You have no right to kick me out of this house.
If Joon Soo's father were to come back to life
and tell me to leave because he can't stand seeing me anymore,
I'd listen then.
If that's not the case, then no one can push me even a step out of this house.
I don't need the brewery or anything else. Pack your bags now!
Don't show your face again, Hyo Seon's uncle.
Joon Soo is back home!
Aigoo, my son. Did you have fun at your kindergarten?
Our only eldest son Goo Joon Soo! Did you have a good time at your kindergarten?
I'm hungry!
We can't let our Goo family's eldest son stay hungry, can we?
Even if the rest of the world is starving, we definitely can't let our Joon Soo go hungry.
Ahjussi.
Ahjussi, what brings you here?
You didn't even call us so how come you directly visit us in person...
Hello.
It's been so long since you left and you're still not here?
How come you're taking longer than me when I left after you did?
Okay, come quickly!
Ahjussi.
No, the thing is that I thought the rice would come first.
But what am I supposed to do now if I arrive before the rice, Hyo Seon?
These punks were drinking some rice wine during the day before they left,
saying they would break through all the alcohol jars, so they said they loaded up late.
You said rice, Ahjussi.
Geez lazy ass punks. I'll twist their mouths.
We were uh voting a bit at the cooperative.
And just one punk said not to subcontract anymore,
I used about 1 dwe (1.8 L) of makgeolli as a bribe, so be sure to pay that back later.
Geez lazy bums.
Ahjussi.
Ahjussi!
Ahjussi, thank you.
Ahjussi.
Thank you very much.
When they bring the rice, unload it carefully. I'm leaving now.
Ahjussi, how can you just leave?
Please eat before you leave.
I have some business to care of in the provincial office. I only stopped on the way there.
By the way, I told the provincial office about here.
I don't know if you can get some support or not,
There are things that Dae Seong did when he was alive too and stuff.
What's the point of just saying things. Let's see.
I'm leaving.
You did this, Hyo Seon.
You did very well.
Don't do that.
What?
Don't talk to me in such a gentle way.
I'm not smart so it really, really confuses me.
Come to think about it,
ever since you first came into my house,
until now when you've officially rejected me,
whether you're comforting or scolding me,
even until the moment you told me to stop acting like a child and leaning on you,
you were always gentle, Oppa.
Even if the world collapses,
you made me think that as long as I'm holding onto you, I'd survive and be safe.
It was you, Oppa.
It doesn't make sense for you to be so kind
after you've pushed me so far to the edge of the safety rail.
The problem with the rice has been resolved.
Just like when Dad was here, he said that he'd supply the rice to us.
Unni, are things going well for you?
I'm waiting for you to call me because I don't want to be a nuisance and disturb you.
When you have free time, please call me back.
Written by Dae Seong True Winemakers' Staff member, Goo Hyo Seon.
You have a new e-mail.
Success!
I obtained accurate data on the yeast.
I've sent the results to the research lab, so please discuss the schedule with them to process it.
An industrial sized culturing machine used to create freeze dried yeast in bulk,
a freeze drying machine. To negotiate the vacuum seal machine rental with Miura-san.
I'll be back with some good news in a few days.
And also, I'm considering the name of the yeast to be "Daeseong Saccharomyces
Ask for Hyo Seon's opinion. Get back to me.
- Hyo Seon is home
- Hyo Seon is home!
Joon Soo, we did it!
We did it?
We did it! I said we did it!
Mom.
Mom!
Dad!
Dad. Dad?
Dad.
Unni did it.
Eun Jo did it.
Dad, Eun Jo did it.
Dae Seong...
Daeseong Saccharomyces.
She said that she's going to name the yeast after you and not after her.
Do you dislike it that yeast is being named after you?
If you dislike it, tell me.
Because then I'll tell Eun Jo to name it after her.
You don't, right?
You like that it'll be named after you, right?
I like it too.
Director Hong Gi Jeong.
The pathways of complement activation
Folk Bar.
We're preparing to open the second store..
The problem was that the same taste of alcohol didn't come from all the jars because the yeast wasn't producing it.
Since the yeast is too sensitive,
any minimal sort of alteration to the environment causes the yeast to change,
then the taste of the alcohol will change too.
So that's why Eun Jo went to Japan to use a certain machine
to find out the conditions to make the taste produced by the yeast uniform.
And also, that yeast has been named Daeseong Saccharomyces.
- But Dong Soo...
- What?
Isn't your magazine reporting about us too much?
The magazine has been writing about us three times out of the four publications in one month.
Is it too much?
Did I say I was writing an article for my magazine?
I thought you said this was an interview.
I'm going to post this on my blog.
What?
Do you think online advertising is a joke?
My blog gets an average of approximately a thousand visitors a day. Is it ridiculous?
No, that's not it.
When's Eun Jo coming back?
I'm not sure yet.
When Eun Jo comes back, I have to interview her too.
In my opinion, my blog has more readers than our magazine.
I'm going to upload a few of your photos on my blog.
You can go now.
Come with Eun Jo next time. Don't come alone.
It's Goo Hyo Seon!
We love you Goo Hyo Seon! You're our angel, Goo Hyo Seon!
You're our angel, Goo Hyo Seon!
Wait, wait a moment. Are you done?
No!
- Please give me an autograph.
- Please take a picture with me!
I think you've taken enough photos. Please remember to leave us good comments.
Our bubble girl, Goo Hyo Seon!
We love you Goo Hyo Seon!`
You're our angel, Goo Hyo Seon!
Unni, please give me an autograph!
Japan said they would purchase the machine domestically (in Korea) and then lease it to us.
I'll be back.
Okay.
- Marry us!
They're some internet fan club.
They came after seeing our commercial, Dong Soo's article and blog.
Marry us!
You're a star.
- Marry us!
Hey, what to do!
You're our angel, Goo Hyo Seon! We love you!
MMM
- Hello?
- When are you coming?
What's wrong?
I'm going tomorrow. Why?
You haven't been sleeping or eating properly there, have you?
What about the machine? Did you see it?
Hang up and go back to the hotel and rest right away.
- Did you see the machine?
- I'm going to see it. I'm going right now.
- Stop acting up and go back to the hotel immediately...
- Call me back after you see the machine.
As commanded Hong Ju will sell its takju for an even lower price
so give up on Daeseong True Winemakers' takju
is what we have told Miura-san.
What was their response?
They said it's impossible due to their contract with Daeseong True Winemakers, but...
But what?
They said to give them time to think about it.
Okay. You may go now.
- But...
- What is it?
There are opinions that dumping our takju isn't wi--
What are you talking about?
Even if they were to propose an even lower price, I had planned on doing so.
Leave now.
Yes.
We're going to start the yeast production from tomorrow, so please be prepared.
As the curds have finished, I timed it so we could start the new takju production.
I'll ask this favor of you, Factory Manager.
Yes, good night.
Sunbaenim. What will happen if I stab you in the back and reveal who you are?
In other words, you were a spy.
Isn't that right?
Do whatever you want.
I don't care about what happens. Do whatever you want.
You doubt me?
Why didn't you do it when you could've done it before?
- What did you say?
- There were so many opportunities.
You didn't take advantage of any of those opportunities. What's the reason?
- That's...
- It's because of Eun Jo, isn't it?
You fat kid from Namhae, Han Jeong Woo.
I'm also the same.
The brewery only needs to get over this crisis.
As long as we get over this crisis and the factory gets back to its feet,
I don't care what happens after.
If you can only turn a blind eye to me until then, I'll be very grateful.
Yes, hello. This is Hong Ki Hoon from Dae Seong True Wine Makers.
Joon Soo.
Joon Soo, you weren't sleeping yet?
I want to sleep with you, Noona.
Why?
What about Mom?
She smells of alcohol.
Mom.
Why are you drinking alone, Mom?
Pour me some.
Mom.
I don't know what kind of a wench I am either...
No. I don't know what kind of person I am either.
My heart seems to hurt so much as if it'll shatter
and in an instant it becomes like nothing.
Mom... What's wrong with you?
What I'm most afraid of is
living my life without that person.
Your father said this.
He said he was afraid of continuing to live his life without me.
I read it, read it again, and read it once more.
I read it till my eyes felt like they were going to fall out.
Mom.
What's the use of all that?
He's no longer by my side.
He can't protect me from the wind and rain anymore.
Mom.
You're that person's daughter?
Yes, Mom.
You're the daughter of that foolish Ahjussi?
Yes.
If he knows that his life without me will be scary...
Then, why did he abandon me to live a life without him?
♫  In your name when tears appear  ♫
That's what I'm saying...
♫  I can't bear it  ♫
You are the daughter of that foolish Ahjussi.
♫  I'll call out your name again  ♫
♫  Even if there are wounds left in my heart now  ♫
Mom.
♫  I am told to forget about you  ♫
Can you call me 'My baby' just once?
♫  but even if I bite my lips and bear it  ♫
♫  You are the only one who is my person  ♫
♫  I am living day after day  ♫
♫  In your name when tears appear again,  ♫
♫  I can't bear it  ♫
What shampoo do you use, my baby?
♫  I call out your name again  ♫
What the hell? What's the point of working to survive if you've worked yourself to death?
Let's just go quietly, Jeong Woo. I can't stand the noise.
- I guess I 'm going to the hospital.
- Go to the winery.
I'm going to the hospital.
Go to the winery.
You girl... really.
Dae Seong True Winemakers
What on earth is that supposed to mean?
Your explanation is insufficient!
Hello? Hello?!
What's going on?
Unni.
They said they're going to cancel the machine rental.
What?
Their order too.
What did you say?
They're cancelling their order too.
What's that supposed to mean?
Even right before I came here, it was firmly promised.
What's wrong with you?
Unni. Unni! What to do?
- Unni! Oppa...
- What's wrong?
- What?
- Unni.
Let's go outside.
What's wrong with Noona?
Open the door.
Move.
Hello, this is Dae Seong True Winemakers. (In Jpapanese)
Regarding the cancellation of your order,
I'd like to hear a detailed explanation.
Go to the winery.
Lay back down.
It's just fatigue. Just go to the winery.
I said lay back down, you wench!
You have a call from Dae Seong True Winemakers' Goo Hyo Seon. Should I put her through?
My name is Hong Gi Jeong.
Please sit down.
I don't have much time. Please tell me what you want.
The Japanese contract signed with us, you...
I didn't come out to discuss that with a young child.
What did you say?
What does your contract have to do with us?
We just made a deal with Miyura-san.
Miyura-san is the one that debated the options and decided to go with us.
By any chance, are you going to bring up fair play or something along those lines?
- We had to go through so much to...
- I don't care what you had to do to get this contract.
I also had a hard time getting this contract.
All I did was make a proposal to them, regardless of your company's actions.
If there's been an issue that came up regarding a breach of contract, that's between you and Miyura.
It has nothing to do with me.
Are you the older sister or the younger sister?
Are you the one who's been researching yeast?
Why are you curious about that?
If you're that person, I have something I want to say to you.
And what is it that you want to say?
Are you researching yeast?
No.
Then you must be the younger sister.
Please tell your unni that I'd like to meet her.
I wondered whether you are the older sister or not so that's why I came out.
If I had known there would be a child who knows nothing about the world,
I wouldn't have wasted my time on purpose.
Look here!
Look here! Look here!
Oppa.
Eun Jo was admitted to the hospital for a day.
Your mother will watch her, so she says to sleep with Joon Soo.
It's Hong Joo Ga.
Instead of ours, they said they would accept the Hong Ju Brewery Takju for nearly nothing.
How did you know that?
Then, does that mean you knew already?
How did you...?
Why is Hong Joo Ga doing this to us?
They're already a large company,
and defeating such a small company like us won't even benefit that much.
That scumbag... Does he think I'll leave him alone?
I'm supposed to meet Dong Soo tomorrow.
I'll use all of my strength to prevent him from doing this.
That... Scumbag.
I met Hong Joo Ga's heir Hong Gi Jeong.
You met that person?
I won't leave him be.
I'm just not going to let him do this.
It's Dad's handwriting!
Your father said this.
He said he was afraid of continue living his life without me.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay. No problem at all.
You're going to rest today, right?
I'm going to go out after I change my clothes.
You can leave now, Mom.
If you and I are kicked out of this house today,
what are we going to do?
Mom, I can't hear anything you're saying.
The contract we made isn't going well. This is our first priority.
If this contract goes wrong, Mom and I will have to pack our bags
even if we're not kicked out of this house.
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love  ♫
♫  My bruised heart is shouting so that  ♫